[{"question": " okay, ross, i realise that you didn't expect to walk in and see that, but.. let me explain, okay?", "answer": " we weren't doing anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " rach, he just saw us.", "answer": " shhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " but what you saw, that is the extent of it, okay? one kiss.", "answer": " no, come on, that is a lie. we also kissed in barbados. joey : dude, chill!  okay, we also kissed in barbados, but we didn't plan it, okay? and the only reason that that happened was because i saw you kissing charlie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah, you started it! i've got to chill.", "answer": " look, we probably should have talked to you about this before it ever happened, but..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " we feel so terrible about this, ross.", "answer": " yeah, but it did happen, so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " ross?", "answer": " ross?  can we just close the door? opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " ross, say something. anything.", "answer": " so you two are..? joey and rachel: yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " and have you .. ed?", "answer": " no, no, no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " no, no, no!", "answer": " but if i hadn't walked in here, would you..?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " no, no!", "answer": " ross, this is not how we wanted you to find out about this. you have every right to go nuts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i'm not going nuts. do you see me go nuts?", "answer": " no, but you know what i mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hey, hey, hey... if you two are happy, then i'm happy for you.  i'm fine!", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " absolutely.  i'm fine! totally fine. i don't know why it's coming out all loud and squeaky, 'cause really,  i'm fine. i'm not saying i wasn't a little surprised to see you guys kissing. i mean, at first i was like..  but now that i've had time to absorb it; lovin' this.", "answer": " ross..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " it's all working out! me &amp; charlie, and you two. you know what we should do?", "answer": " calm ourselves?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " no. we should all have dinner. yes, we'll do it tomorrow night. i'll cook!!", "answer": " look, don't you think that will be a little weird?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " god, this adoption stuff is so overwhelming. there's inter-country adoption, dependency adoption.. there are so many ways to go, and this is like the biggest decision of our lives.", "answer": " there's a hair in my coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey, have you seen frank jr., 'cause he's meeting me here with the triplets.", "answer": " you know, it's funny. every time you say &quot;triplets,&quot; i immediately think of three hot blonde 19-year olds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " that's sweet. drink your hair.", "answer": " hey, what's all this stuff?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, they're brochures from different adoption agencies.", "answer": " ooh, babies! oh, this one is so cute, get this one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " that's not really how it works.", "answer": " oh, how does it work?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i don't know!", "answer": " well, if you're having a hard time, you should talk to my friends, bill and colleen. they adopted a kid. i'm sure they'd help you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " that's not what we talked about!!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " good to see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " good to see you, too.", "answer": " hi frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " hi, how you doin'?", "answer": " oh, my goodness, they've all gotten so big!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " which one is which again?", "answer": " oh, that's frank jr. jr. pulling the tampons out of the lady's purse. and that's chandler climbing on chandler, and that's leslie throwing bagels at him. monica : &quot;willing to adopt triplets?&quot; no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " ah, can i just say i know we're doing this for ross, and that's cool, but if it was up to me, this is not what we'd be doing on our first date.", "answer": " well, what would we be doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i'd take you out for a romantic night. some champagne, fancy dinner, feel you up on the carriage ride home...", "answer": " feel me up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hey, charlie!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " hi, hi. so.. dreading this?", "answer": " oh, you bet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so, did you bring a little something for ross?", "answer": " actually.. it's stuff you left at my apartment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh. oh, thanks.", "answer": " and you know, you can just give me my stuff whenever you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i thought i heard voices! hi charlie!  hi joey.  and.. oh! you're gonna have to introduce me to your new girlfriend.  i'm just kidding, i know rachel, i know.  come, please come in. come in.", "answer": " okay, well, we brought you some wine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " uh, actually, that's..", "answer": " underwear, a toothbrush, and van halen cd. i can use all these things!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " gosh, ross, you know, you seem a little...", "answer": " what? fine? because i am! aren't you? aren't you? aren't you? you see? who else is fine?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " okay, listen, hey, ross. why don't you try to relax, okay? maybe have a drink.", "answer": " you know what? that is a very good idea. i'm gonna go make a pitcher of margaritas.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh, god. so adorable. look at them sleeping there like angels.", "answer": " yeah, i really cherish these moments, 'cause before you know it, they're gonna be awake again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " well, they may be a handful, but they're so cute.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh, god, the last time i babysat them, they did the funniest thing..", "answer": " i haven't slept in four years!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " that's a, that's a long time.", "answer": " you just don't know how hard it is, phoebe. there's just so many of them. you know, two i can handle. two's great. you just hold one in each hand, but what do i do when the third one runs at me with his bike helmet on. i've got no more hands to protect my area! there's three of them, phoebe, three!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah, i know, frank. i counted them when they were coming out of my area.", "answer": " sometimes i think that.. oh, no, no, no, i can't say it, it's too horrible. no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " no, i can't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh my god, frank, are you thinking of leaving? because i didn't have those triplets so you could just run out on them!", "answer": " oh, no! i would never do that. no. i just was thinking that, you know, maybe you could take one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " thank you so much for seeing us. phoebe has told us such great things about you guys.", "answer": " oh, please, we're happy to help.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " we went through the same thing when we were adopting.", "answer": " so, a lot of malfunctioning wee-wees and hoo-hoos in this room, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " i mean, you have a lovely home.", "answer": " well, we appreciate anything you can tell us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " it's pretty much all the information you need.", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " everything is broken down into categories, and then cross-referenced, and then colour-coded to correspond with the forms in the back.", "answer": " thank you.  i think i just had a tiny orgasm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i know the process is frustrating, but it's so worth it. adopting owen was the best thing that ever happened to us.", "answer": " that's great.  can i see the book?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " you want me to wash my hands first, don't you?", "answer": " it's.. it's just so pretty and white.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i would have told him to do it too.", "answer": " can i adopt you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey, you must be owen.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i'm chandler. hey, i was in the scouts too.", "answer": " you were?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah, in fact my father was a den-mother.", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you know how to use a compass?", "answer": " i have a badge in it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you do? that's fantastic!", "answer": " you wanna see it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i'd love to, but i gotta get back to talking to your parents. they're telling us all about how they adopted you.", "answer": " what?!?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i'm adopted?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " the first batch of margaritas was not so great, but the second batch is gooooood.", "answer": " well, maybe the next batch, we could all get some.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh, guys, this is fun, isn't it? you know? just the four of us. just hangin'.", "answer": " dude, are you okay? and when are the fajitas gonna be ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i'm fine! hey, i'm great! i'm just.. i'm just proud of us. there's no weirdness, no tension.", "answer": " no awareness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " look, charlie, i just want you to know. ross is just having a little trouble adjusting to the thought of joey and me. you know, he normally doesn't drink like this.", "answer": " oh, you know what? this is nothing. my father is a raging alcoholic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " fajitas! be careful, very hot plate, very hot plate!!", "answer": " ross, you don't even have oven mitts on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " okay, well, this is crazy. can't seriously be talking about me taking one of your kids, can we?", "answer": " no, of course we're not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " insane.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " alice would never go for it, right?", "answer": " oh, i don't know, she's pretty tired, too, i think we've got her onboard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " well, just you know, for argument's sake, you know, hypothetically. which one would you be willing to give up?", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " frank jr.jr.?", "answer": " oh, you'd be getting a really good one. i mean, you know, he's really funny. like, the other day he made up this joke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " what's green and says &quot;hey, i'm a frog&quot;? a talking frog!  oh, no, you can't have him, he's too funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " well, alright, that's fine. what about leslie?", "answer": " oh, no, no. not leslie. no, she's, she's the only one that knows how to burp the alphabet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " alright, so that leaves chandler.", "answer": " oh, no, no, you can't have chandler, no. no, no. she's my little genius. i got big hopes for her. she's gonna be a doctor or a realtor..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " wow, frank. i think we just ran out of kids.", "answer": " oh, i think you're right. oh, wow. phoebe, i don't think i can give one of them up. i mean, you know, they drive me crazy, but they're my babies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i'm sorry, frank. i didn't realise things were so bad. you know, i'll help out more. i can - i can babysit any time you want. you name the day, and i'll be there.", "answer": " how about tomorrow?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well, that's not good. but you know, i can move some stuff around, and i'll be there. you and alice just take the whole day together.", "answer": " you'd do that for us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " where are bill and colleen?", "answer": " they're in the kitchen getting something to eat. can you believe how nice they are?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " we have to leave!!", "answer": " why? what did you do in the bathroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i didn't get to the bathroom. i bumped into owen on the way, and he didn't know he was adopted. and there's a slight chance i may have told him.", "answer": " oh my god, where's my purse? no, you know what? i can replace everything in there. get that binder, and let's go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " some little snacks for everybody. oh, you don't have to eat the sour worms. those are for owen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i'll go get him in a second. by the way, you should know we haven't told him he's adopted yet.", "answer": " but kids are so intuitive. don't you think on some level he already knows?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i'm adopted?!", "answer": " see? intuitive!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " what? where did you hear that?", "answer": " he told me! and he paid me 50 dollars not to tell.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " which technically now you should give back!", "answer": " you told him he's adopted?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i'm so sorry, but you should have a sign out there or something. or at least whisper it to people when they come in the door. &quot;owen doesn't know he's adopted, and he also thinks that santa is real.&quot;", "answer": " he isn't?! chandler : we have to get out of here, baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " everyone? i would like to make a toast to rachel and joey.", "answer": " ooy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " and to love. ah, love. l-o-v-e, love. l is for life. and what is life without love?", "answer": " oh my god, are we supposed to answer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " dude, are you okay?", "answer": " totally.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " ross, you don't seem okay. ross : i'm sorry, it must be the pressure of entertaining. i think everyone would feel better if we had some flan.", "answer": " wait, ross. ross. i - i have to take off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " i'm sorry, i have a really early class in the morning, but this has been lovely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " wasn't it? and you thought it would be awkward with joey and that you never really liked rachel.", "answer": " you're on fire! i'll call you in the morning, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " alright.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " god, rachel, what ross just said that is just so..", "answer": " oh, that's okay, girls tend not to like me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " okay, i guess it's just flan for three! hey, hey, that rhymed!", "answer": " you know what, ross? i think we're gonna take off too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh, oh. of course. god, i'm so stupid. you guys are a couple now. i mean, you probably just want to be alone.", "answer": " no, no, it's just that it's getting late...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " you know what? i think i'm gonna stay here and make sure he's okay.", "answer": " yeah, that's probably a good idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah. i'll see you in the morning.", "answer": " uh-huh. okay. you know what, joey, i don't think he's ever gonna be okay with this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " morning. here you go.", "answer": " thanks. did you stay here all night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " so you took off my pants and shoes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " no, no, no. you actually did that when you were dancing to the chicago-soundtrack. look, ross, about, about rachel and i. listen, you don't have to worry about that, okay? because nothing is gonna happen.", "answer": " what do you mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well, she and i said from the beginning that we weren't gonna do anything unless you were okay with it. and clearly..", "answer": " hey, what are you talking about? i'm fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " it's okay, ross, alright? i totally understand. of course you're not fine. you're.. you're ross and rachel.", "answer": " except we're not. i mean, we haven't been a couple in like, six years. oh my god, is that right? has it been that long?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " that's what i hear, yeah.", "answer": " this is crazy. i mean, six years? and because of me you guys aren't gonna be together? can i ask you something? really, what is this thing with you and rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " come on, i mean, you know me, you know...", "answer": " joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i'm crazy about her.", "answer": " and she feels the same way?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i think so.", "answer": " well, then, maybe it's time we all moved on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah, but, ross, i mean, you're not okay with it.", "answer": " no, but i wanna be. hey, i will be. besides, i'm with charlie, right? oh my god, i'm still with charlie, aren't i? i mean, she didn't see the dance, did she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " no, no, no, no, that was - that was just for me. are you sure about this?", "answer": " yeah, i'm sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " hey, phoebs", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " uhm, we just wanna give you a heads-up. bill and colleen hate us.", "answer": " owen didn't know he was adopted, and monica told him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " still, he had to find out sometime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}]